{
    "subject": "resource/Imad_Abu_Zahra",
    "predicate": "property/nationality",
    "object": "Palestinian",
    "human_readable": "Imad Abu Zahra's nationality is Palestinian.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9392889142036438,
            "question": "Is Imad Abu Zahra Palestinian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8824767470359802,
            "question": "What is Imad Abu Zahra's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7317838668823242,
            "question": "What nationality defines Imad Abu Zahra's identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6087890267372131,
            "question": "To which country does Imad Abu Zahra belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5369817614555359,
            "question": "Based on his nationality, what can you infer about Imad Abu Zahra's experiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5085598230361938,
            "question": "Where is Imad Abu Zahra from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4532734751701355,
            "question": "Where was Imad Abu Zahra likely born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4477445185184479,
            "question": "How would you describe Imad Abu Zahra's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4397137463092804,
            "question": "What national identity is associated with Imad Abu Zahra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29564711451530457,
            "question": "What cultural heritage does Imad Abu Zahra possess?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Imad Abu Zahra's nationality is Palestinian.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2004_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What national identity is associated with Imad Abu Zahra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2004_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Imad Abu Zahra's origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2004_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Imad Abu Zahra likely born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2004_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2004_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as Imad Abu Zahra's nationality is consistently referred to as Palestinian throughout the provided text."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which indicate that Imad Abu Zahra was a Palestinian freelance photographer. Therefore, the statement \"Imad Abu Zahra's nationality is Palestinian\" is supported by the context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}